Dear, we've got mail from Rinko!
Master Kunon passed the
exam with flying colors
and was placed in the advanced class,
the highest class in the magic school!
Wow!
That's our Kunon.
He sort of overdid the exam and
painted the school yard red.
But he got into the advanced
class, so all is good!
He's called Kunon Gurion of the sea
of blood incident, or a troublemaker,
but it's the fruit of Master
Kunon's talent! It's all good!
It's not all good!
It's unacceptable to cause such
problems right after enrollment!
As a punishment, I'm not
sending money for a month!
Dear, that's too cruel.
Allowances are forbidden?
Okay! That's how the magic school does it.
I like it!
I don't think it's a laughing matter.
Are you saying advanced students
are supposed to make their own living?
Yes, that's correct.
I cannot accept that.
THE SAINT'S FINANCIAL PROBLEM
Is there a problem, Reyes?
I came here to learn magic.
I have no time to figure
out how to make ends meet.
You're in the advanced class, where
we foster top-tier sorcerers,
and one of the conditions for being
top-tier is being able to make money.
Shall I break it down for you?
If you can't make money on your own,
you'll never be top-tier.
One and a half million necca a month?
That's your living expenses?!
A lady needs money to
invest in herself, right?
I have two maids who double as my guards.
So on top of my living expenses,
I need to pay their salaries.
I see.
What will you do?
I haven't the faintest idea.
An individual research lab?
Yes, every student in the advanced
class is assigned a lab room.
Nice!
And you want us to pay for this, too?
The use of the lab is free.
You're responsible for the medicine
and books for your research, though.
You're free to study hard or slack off,
but if you don't earn enough credits,
you'll be demoted to the Second Level.
Credits?
Credits are earned for
experiments and achievements in magic.
The achievements acknowledged by the
professors will be awarded credits,
and they affect your promotion.
Good luck on your work.
Thank you. I'm pretty sure I can manage.
My master and I have made
quite a bit of money.
With Zeon? Tch.
He didn't even pay me part-time, though.
My master found his job as a magical
engineer at this school, right?
How lucky is he to have found
a job for life in magic?
I've dreamed of working in the field
of magic since I was small, too.
Wow. I didn't expect you to be
so serious about your future.
Right? Right? Aren't I amazing?!
Listen, what kind of jobs
will you do with light magic?
I'm so interested!
If you don't mind,
tell me about it after this.
I can take us to a really
great magic parfait shop!
No, thank you.
Master Kunon! Dinner is ready... oh.
You're making me jealous.
Can I have one in my room, too?
Did something happen at school?
The saint always turns me down.
That won't do, Master Kunon.
What won't do?
Listen to me, Master Kunon.
You don't want to be pushy with girls.
A gentleman respects a lady's
wishes more than anything.
Okay.
And you shouldn't be alone with a girl.
It causes unnecessary misunderstandings.
Do you understand, Master Kunon?
I do. I'll be careful.
I have to nudge him
towards the right track.
My sister's idea of a gentleman
is kind of skewed, so...
In any case,
will you be able to make money yourself
since you can't get an allowance?
Yes. I'm sure I can pay
your salary just fine.
That's what I wanted to hear!
I asked the school and confirmed you
are not allowed to receive support
from the Holy Kingdom or donations.
Just like the guidelines said.
They said one is forbidden from receiving
money and goods from any party.
I don't need to get paid.
Are you sure? That would be helpful.
Sorry, I lied.
I just wanted to say it.
Understood.
Your healing magic can't be
used for business purposes.
One and a half million necca.
One and a half million...
What's the matter?
Oh, Reyes.
Kunon started a business,
and it was an instant hit.
You'd like a 60-minute course?
Yes. I pulled an all-nighter
for an experiment.
Can I really get deep sleep here?
Of course.
I will personally guarantee
you a well-rested time.
Well then, let us go
to the secret flower garden for
you and me and a few other people.
I'm sorry, but all the slots are full,
so please wait for about 30 minutes.
This is impressive.
I-I can't do this...
Thirty more minutes until
the flower garden.
Oh, hello.
What in the world did you start here?
A Sleep Sanctuary.
Sleep?
It's true. The person who just
went in is already sound asleep.
What are those beds?
They're water beds I
created with my magic.
It's the only thing my master
acknowledged and complimented.
Zeon, giving a compliment?
Tch.
Making sleep a business...
I never thought about that.
Once you start experiments or research,
you get sucked in and pull
all-nighters, you know?
Huh? Master, the sky is
somehow getting lighter.
You idiot, it's called a white night.
Okay, it's not like we
stayed up all night,
so it's fine for us to continue, right?
Yeah. But I'm sure it'll be
a white night tomorrow, too.
You two must go to sleep already!
So I figured I could
offer them a nice, brief nap.
Your request for an additional
lab space is granted,
so make this available
to professors, too.
But charging professors feels...
Don't worry about it!
Because there are tons
of people like that here!
MISS A FROM FIRST LEVEL
It ruins you with comfort.
MR. B FROM SECOND LEVEL
I feel refreshed, as if I slept half
a day with only a 60-minute nap.
MR. C, WITH 25 YEARS
OF TEACHING EXPERIENCE
Two, even three nights of no sleep
feels like just one all-nighter!
Enjoy your time.
Next?
The 60-minute course, please.
Thank you. Is this your first time here?
Kunon Gurion.
Zeonly's student.
Life is hard.
Saint Reyes, if I may
offer a suggestion...
Why don't you discuss
it with your teachers?
I have.
And?
They suggested that I should
ask Kunon Gurion for advice.
A boyfriend who hits on you, was it?
You're so popular.
He's just a classmate.
Oh? And what do your other classmates say?
They said it'd be best to ask
for advice from Kunon Gurion.
Why should I ask for advice
from someone so frivolous?
If I have to name the emotion
I'm feeling right now,
this must be humiliation.
You want my advice?
I'm ready to listen!
Personally, I never wanted to rely on you.
Who knows what you will
ask of me in return?
A gentleman would never prey
on a lady's vulnerability.
You just owe me one.
And I'd rather not owe you anything.
Anyhow, here's my situation.
Hold on.
Before you begin, can you
call Professor Sayfie here?
That was an appropriate decision.
Sorry to bother you, Professor Sayfie.
I thought, as a gentleman, I should
avoid being alone with a lady.
I didn't expect that from you.
I heard about your situation.
You have no way of making
money, is that correct?
Yes.
How about healing wounds with your magic?
That would surely make you a lot of money.
My healing magic is a holy power
bestowed from my ancestors and god.
I can't use it to make money.
If that's not a possibility, how's this?
Spell verification and
archival reports of experiments.
Yes. There are sorcerers who
want to buy these as data.
But coming from us, the new
students at this school,
our work may not be as valuable.
You can't use healing magic and
have no capital for a business.
Learning the know-how takes time.
How about purification magic?
Can you use that for products?
That's not a problem.
Then would you like to create
and sell magic tools with me?
Magic tools?
Hold on!
A hit with a magic tool is huge.
If your product sells well,
there are bound to be problems
if you share the rights to it.
Ms. Reyes is the lead, even though
we'll be creating it together.
She's in need of money right now,
so let's not worry about what happens
after we create the magic tool.
Well, as long as you're okay with it.
So? Would you like to do it?
Very well.
Great! Light magic experiments!
Hello, Professor Sureyya.
Your skin is so plump and
smooth, just like an icy road.
It's thanks to that water bed.
My fatigue is gone, and my skin looks
good. Now I know why it's been so popular.
This professor... is a light sorcerer?
You must be the rumored saint.
Nice to meet you. I'm Sureyya Gaulin,
a professor with the light attribute.
Nice to meet you. I'm Reyes Saint-Lance.
Thank you for escorting them,
Professor Sureyya.
My pleasure.
Here's what you've asked for.
Thank you very much.
Seeds of shi-shilla?
Yes. The sacred herb, shi-shilla.
We're going to grow it.
That's not possible.
The sacred herb shi-shilla can
only grow in holy land.
That's what I hear.
I did some research on sacred
herbs and holy land.
Holy land is a place imbued
with holy magic
and purification power, right?
I've been to a holy land once.
The land was purified by
holy magical power.
That's it.
What's it?
You can use purification
magic for business, correct?
So I'm wondering if we can
artificially create holy land.
Create holy land?
The personal spell of the saint, Sanctum.
That might do the trick, don't you think?
Using Sanctum?
A holy barrier created by Sanctum will
reproduce the state of holy land.
There are records that
document their similarities,
so I think it is worth a try.
That's what Kunon came
to talk to me about.
I'm extremely intrigued!
All right, go ahead.
I did it.
Oh wow! Oh wow! Oh wow!
Yes! Sprouts of shi-shilla!
Incredible! I must write down
everything that just happened.
Amazing! A barrier of light magic!
Oh my, one book won't be
enough to document this!
So he gets like this
when it comes to magic.
He actually wanted to experiment,
so he really wasn't hitting on me.
And what do we do now?
What? Wanna go out for some tea?
That's fine too, but I'd
rather have lunch with you.
So he is hitting on me.
About the sacred herb.
We process it to make medicine.
Sacred herb shi-shilla
is rare and expensive.
If we succeed, making 1.5
million necca isn't a dream!
This is worth 1.5 million necca?
I gave it a lot of thought
and came up with nothing.
But he came up with a way to make
money with magic in such a short time.
What? Were you admiring my profile?
Did you fall for me again?
I wasn't admiring you to begin with.
I'm glad your one million necca
didn't go to waste, Kunon.
Indeed.
What was the money for?
The price of these seeds.
One seed is 200,000 necca, so the
total was one million necca.
You pay for what you use in your
magic experiments, remember?
But I don't have that kind of money.
It's for Kunon.
But the deal was that they'd be free with
the success of the cultivation of the
herb and the report on its growth.
If it didn't succeed,
were you going to...?
Yes.
So I'm glad it was a success.
Thank you. You saved me.
If I have to define what I'm feeling
right now, I think I'm feeling sorry.
I caused you trouble.
I'm sorry.
I'd rather hear "thank
you" than "I'm sorry."
I prefer that sentence.
Thank you.
Did you fall for me again?
I've never fallen for you.
Oh my!
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
It's wonderful!
Grind the petals, mix in
the dried iyo grass, and...
This is almost done.
Now you can finish up.
Yes, ma'am.
A-rubu.
These are unmistakably pills of
sacred herb shi-shilla.
At this purity, they're worth
1.5... No, 2 million necca.
So much food. Are you sure?
It's to celebrate closing the deal.
It's a gentleman's joy to dedicate
his wallet to attractive ladies.
Please order whatever you like.
Master Kunon Gurion. Thank you!
Now we can get paid.
And you negotiated a long-term
contract with the guild for us.
Thank you for everything.
I got to write a report on light magic,
not to mention have lunch
with you, so I'm happy.
Thank you for the food.
Cheers!
That lunch was 220,000 necca.
I heard they had to starve themselves
for a while, but still...
Especially the wine.
Those maids drank the vintage wine
worth 20,000 necca like water.
Even if it's for ladies, I should learn
not to say, "Order whatever you want."
Well, I learned a good lesson.
Hey, welcome back.
How did Reyes's medicine go?
It went very well.
Except for the wine.
What are you two up to?
You want a nap?
No. Actually, we're not really
sure where to begin ourselves.
Oh, is that so?
Wait, that's all?
Kunon, can I ask for your advice?
If you were ladies, I would've
done everything in my power.
I figured as much.
Then will you help with my ideas?
I'd like you to make
bacon I can eat, Hank.
Bacon?!
And I want Riyah to fly.
Fly?!
Yeah, that's right.
I slept so well.
This is a sanctuary.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Nothing better to do?
No way. Of course not.
Gathering information, I bet.
I'm sure they're here for the same reason.
To get Kunon Gurion!
Next episode: "Flying and
Roasting and Being Invited."
NEXT EPISODE:
FLYING AND ROASTING AND BEING INVITED